A big equity trade has happened on this as well, so
Reda, this is also another counter which should be on your watch,
ICS Lord, I had to
take opinion from Wagle sahab on this, Wagle sahab, 1.4
equity trade has just happened on this, today there is
also a report from Morgan Stanley, who has increased the
target to 185, from 1750 to
around 18753, if this
happens today, then around 1650 is the right entry
level for me, as a trade,
this stock should not go below 1630 for one to two days, on
the upside 1720 1750, this is a view for three to four days,
even for a week, for a few weeks, a few
months, around 1780 to 1800 is my view too, so
this is a positive view for you on the II Lord chart,
you can also see news action coming on this, let's see what kind of move will
come on Asian
i